Guide to the Time Inc. Video Group Records 1934-1989 MS 3009-RG 41
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII.A Time-Life Films: Television Division Records, 1939-1985; 20.55 Linear feet in 22 record cartons
  - Subseries VII.A.5. Co-Production Report Files, 1974-1985; 1.7 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    The Co-Production Reports Files cover the period of 1974 to 1985 and the financial relationship between Time-Life Films and companies it worked with on co-productions. Reports discuss distribution schedules and profits, royalties, production titles, sales, expenditures, and profit losses. There is also a limited amount of correspondence discussing co-production profit statements.
    - BBC Co-Production Reports, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 24-27)
    - BBC Co-Production Reports, 1971-1979 (Offsite-box 3362, Folder 1-8)
    - Co-Production Reports, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 3362, Folder 9-16)
    - Co-Production Reports, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 1-5)
  - Subseries VII.A.6. G.I. Diary Series Files, 1939-1947, 1955-1978; 211948; 11.41 Linear feet in 13 record cartons
    G.I. Diary was a 1978 Time-Life television series that reenacted the experiences of World War II veterans from the war. The Internet Movie Database lists Time-Life Television Productions as the production company.
    Materials in this series include letters written to the production team in response to ads asking for World War II stories, production files, and research materials.
    The G.I. Diary Series Files contain four subsubseries:
    Subsubseries VII.A.6.a. Beverly Smith Files
    Subsubseries VII.A.6.b. Producers Files
    Subsubseries VII.A.6.c. Letter Files
    Subsubseries VII.A.6.d. Research Files
    - Subsubseries VII.A.6.a. Beverly Smith Files, 1936-1979 (bulk, 1978); 3.67 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
      Beverly Smith was an associate producer for the G.I. Diary series that was created by the Time-Life Films television division.
      Beverly Smith's Files focus on the production of the G.I. Diary series and concentrates heavily on the acquisition and use of externally acquired films and stills. Included in this subsubseries are notes, lists of film sequences, preliminary viewing notes, clippings, photocopies of books, shipping orders, film depository forms, lists of contacts, conference notes, first draft outlines, film overviews, production schedules, continuation sheets, veteran interview notes, reel lists, footage and scene lists, lists of captions, photographs, lists of footage, scripts, shot lists, film reproduction forms, shipping forms, negatives and transparencies, stock footage lists, delivery schedules, indexes of army motion pictures for public non-profits use, history center pamphlets, marine corps historical program newsletters, historical publication catalogs, and correspondence. The correspondence in this subsubseries discuss episode writers, footage, reviews and responses, filming plans, photographs, research, film use, veteran interview questions, expenses, lunch meetings, WWII combat art collections, consultants, film orders, and screenings. Early materials consist of clippings and photocopies.
      - Air Force Story: Air Power, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 1)
      - Anzio: Footage, 1978 (Offsite-box 3368, Folder 20)
      - Archive Order Numbers, 1978 (Offsite-box 3368, Folder 21)
      - Atlantic Convoy: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3368, Folder 22)
      - Bastogne: Battle of the Bulge, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 1)
      - "Black" [African American] Units, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 2)
      - Bulge Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 3)
      - Catalogs, 1973-1977 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 4)
      - Catalogs: Archives, 1972 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 3)
      - Catalogs: Army Film [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 4)
      - China, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 5)
      - China/Burma/India (C.B.I), 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 6)
      - China/Burma/India (C.B.I) Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 7-8)
      - Combat America, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 9)
      - Combat Art, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 5)
      - Combat Cameramen, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 10)
      - Consultants, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 6)
      - Contacts: Air Force, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 7)
      - Contacts: Army [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 8)
      - Contacts: L.A., undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 9)
      - Contacts: Marine [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 10)
      - Contacts: Navy [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 11)
      - Convoy Stills: Choices, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 11)
      - Costs and Expenses, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 12)
      - D-Day, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 12)
      - Desert War: Stock Houses, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 13)
      - Doolittli's Raid [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 14)
      - Film: Australia, 1945, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 13)
      - Film: Britain, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 14)
      - Film: Britain [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Film: France, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 15)
      - Film: Norton, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 16)
      - Film: Received, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 15)
      - Film: Received/Slopped, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 16)
      - Film: Research: Costs, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 17)
      - Film: Sicily, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 18)
      - Film: Washington/Quantico, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 17)
      - Film: West Coast, undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 18)
      - Film Labs, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 19)
      - Film Life, Inc., 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 20)
      - Film Orders [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 21)
      - Film Rights, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 22)
      - Film Sources: United States: Color and Black and White, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 23)
      - Flying Tigers [Empty], undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 19)
      - Fox: Movietone, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 20)
      - Franklin (U.S.S), 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 21)
      - GI Christmas: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 22)
      - GI Christmas: Film [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R57)
      - Hook Down, Wheels Down: Clarke Reynolds, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 24)
      - Indemnification, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 23)
      - Indemnification [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R57)
      - Iwo Footage, 1977 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 24)
      - Lab Bills, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 25)
      - Lab Costs, undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 26)
      - Landing in Japan, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 25)
      - The Last Bomb, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 26)
      - Liberation of Paris, 1944, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 27)
      - Library of Paris: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 28)
      - Library of Philippines, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 29)
      - Maudlin, Bill [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 30)
      - McGovern, Daniel, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 27)
      - Medal of Honor, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 31)
      - Memphis Belle, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 32)
      - Merrill's Marauder's [Empty], undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 33)
      - Midway: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 34)
      - Military Leads: Officials, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous: Photographs, 1978, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 36-37)
      - MOH: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 38)
      - N.P.C., 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 29)
      - National Archives, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 30)
      - Navajos: Film, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 39)
      - Navy: Combat Art/Philippines, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 40)
      - Navy: Cut Film, undated (Offsite-box 3369, Folder 41)
      - North Africa, undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 1)
      - North Africa: Footage, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 2)
      - Novik Shot Description, 1978, undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 3-4)
      - NY Military P.R., 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 5)
      - Okinawa, 1959, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 6)
      - Okinawa: Footage, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 7)
      - Orders: Atlantic Convoy, 1941, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 8)
      - Orders: Bulge, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 9)
      - Orders: China/Burma/India (C.B.I), 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 10)
      - Orders: Christmas (Xmas), 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 11)
      - Orders: D-Day, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 12)
      - Orders: Franklin, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 13)
      - Orders: Italy, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 14)
      - Orders: Kamikaze, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 15)
      - Orders: Memphis Belle, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 16)
      - Orders: Midway, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 17)
      - Orders: M.O.H., 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 18)
      - Orders: North Africa, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 19)
      - Orders: Norton, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 20)
      - Orders: Okinawa, 1945, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 21)
      - Orders: Paris, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 22)
      - Orders: Peleliu, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 23)
      - Orders: Philippines, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 24)
      - Orders: Rhine Crossing, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 25)
      - Orders: Saipan, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 26)
      - Orders: San Pietro, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 27)
      - Orders: Sicily, undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 28)
      - Payments and Honorariums, 1977 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 31)
      - Pelilieu, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 29)
      - Pending, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 30)
      - Photographs, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 32)
      - Philippines, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 31)
      - Philippines: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 32)
      - Pilot: Script, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 33)
      - Ploesti, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 33)
      - Prints, 1936-1951, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 34-35)
      - Purchase Order Numbers, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 34)
      - Pyle, Ernie [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 36)
      - Release Forms: Blank, undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 35)
      - Researchers: Text, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 36)
      - Regensburg, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 37)
      - Rhine Crossings, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 38)
      - Rhine Crossings: Fim, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 39)
      - Road to Berlin, 1978 (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 40)
      - Road to Berlin: Footage, undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 41)
      - Road to Berlin: Orders, undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 42)
      - Rosenthal Pix, 1977 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 37)
      - Saipan, 1978 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 1)
      - Sales B.S., 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 38)
      - San Pietro, undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 2)
      - San Pietro: Film [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 3)
      - Schedules, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 39)
      - Series Blurb, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 40)
      - Series Subjects: Storylines, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 41)
      - Series Subjects: General Lists, 1978 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 4)
      - Shot Lists, undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 5-9)
      - Southern France, 1978 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 10)
      - Southern France: Footage, 1978 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 11)
      - Stars in Uniform, undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 12)
      - Stills, 1937-1945 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 13)
      - Stock Footage Requirements, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 42)
      - Submarines, undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 14)
      - True Glory, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 43)
      - Tonight, undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 15)
      - Unsolicited Material, 1977 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 44)
      - USO, undated (Offsite-box 3370, Folder 16)
      - Vet Ads, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 45)
      - Vet Organizations [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 46)
      - Victory at Sea, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 17)
      - Victory at Sea [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R57)
      - War Chronology, undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 47)
      - Women: Film, 1978 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 18)
      - Writers: Memos to, 1978 (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 19)
      - WWII Films, undated (Offsite-box 3371, Folder 20)
    - Subsubseries VII.A.6.b. Producers Files, 1943-1979 (bulk, 1977-1979); 2.2 Linear feet in 3 records cartons
      The Producers' Files contain materials that were mainly created by Mary Freet, production secretary; Beverly (Bev) Smith, associate producer; Janis Klein, producer, and Arthur Holch, executive producer, who were all working on the G.I. Diary series. An array of Time-Life Television staff also worked on the production of the series and appear in the files. The focus of this subseries is on the recording, mixing, and editing work that went into creating and producing the G.I. Diary series as well as the casting process. Included in this subsubseries are notes, clippings, actor information and contact sheets, character break downs, commercial and promotion scripts, audition scripts, pilot scripts, music cue sheets, recording notes, episode synopses, citizen review panel reports, interview guidelines, expense reports, daily production and editing schedules, audition schedules, travel itineraries, program budget reports, lists of consultants, lists of editing rooms, television broadcast schedules, film delivery schedules, production progress reports, research summaries, and correspondence. The correspondence discuss audience responses to the show, audience demographics, scripts, voice over recordings, travel, title card edits, contact information, requests for film and stills, staff lists, job responsibilities, USO and Christmas shows, schedules, and consultants. Especially interesting are the daily schedules, which outline meetings the production staff needed to attend and production deadlines, and the audition scripts which provide details about who was being considered for doing voice over for the series.
      - Actors' Information Sheets, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 48)
      - Actors' Information Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Audience Responses, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 49)
      - Audition Scripts, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 50)
      - Audition Scripts for Women, undated (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 51)
      - Bills: Iwo Jima, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 52)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Expense Reports and Recording Itinerary, 1978 (Offsite-box 3709, Folder 53-57)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Expense Reports and Recording Itinerary: July 14: Iwo Retakes [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R62)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Expense Reports and Recording Itinerary, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 1-3)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Promos and Bills: August 2, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 4)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Promos and Bills: August 2 [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R62)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Recording, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 5)
      - Bridges, Lloyd: Taping: D.C.: 1977 December 6 -7 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 6)
      - Budget, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 7)
      - Bulge, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 8)
      - Cash Requisitions, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 9)
      - Cassettes, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 10-11)
      - Character Break-Downs, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 12)
      - Chronological Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 13-14)
      - Combat Art: Army, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 15)
      - Combat Art: Time-Life, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 16)
      - Combat Photographer, 1944-1945, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 17)
      - Consultants, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 18)
      - Contact List, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 19)
      - Cutting Rooms, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 20)
      - Daily Schedule, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 21-22)
      - Delivery Dates, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 23)
      - Editing Contact Lists, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 24)
      - Episode Hi-Lights, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 25)
      - Film Research: Progress Report, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 26)
      - Film Researchers, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 27)
      - Film Sources: The March of Time: Crusade in Pacific/Europe, 1943 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 28)
      - First Episode and Releases [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R62)
      - GI Christmas Music [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Holch, Arthur: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 29)
      - Holch, Arthur: Expenses, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 30)
      - Holch, Arthur: Expenses [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Iwo Jima: Film Receipts, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 31)
      - Iwo Jima: Graphics, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 32)
      - Iwo Jima: Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 33)
      - Iwo Jima: Music, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 34)
      - Iwo Jima: Releases [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 35)
      - Iwo Jima: Transcripts: Holch, Jacobs Interviews: Washington/Quantico: 1977 October 31 - November 1, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 36)
      - Iwo Jima: Veterans, 1977 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 37)
      - Iwo Jima: Wells, G. Greeley, 1977 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 38)
      - Iwo Jima: Wire Recordings: National Archives, 1977 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 39)
      - M and E (Mixing and Editing) Dates, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 40)
      - Military Contacts, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 41-42)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 43)
      - Music, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 44)
      - Navy Combat Art Collection, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 45)
      - Personal Releases, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 46)
      - Pilot Budget, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 47)
      - Prints, undated (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 48)
      - Production Schedules, 1978 (Offsite-box 3710, Folder 49)
      - Program Cue Sheets, undated (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 1)
      - Program Format, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 2)
      - Progress Reports, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 3)
      - Projected Series Schedule, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 4)
      - Promo: Announcement, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 5)
      - Promo: Reel: Miscellaneous, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 6)
      - Promo and Voice Over: Auditions, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 7)
      - Promo and Voice Over: Auditions and Recording Notes, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 8)
      - Promo and Voice Over: Recording, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 9)
      - Promos, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 10)
      - Publicity, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 11)
      - Ratings, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 12)
      - Release Letter to be Sent to, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 13)
      - Release Letters to be Sent to [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Research Subject File, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 14)
      - Reviews and Press Clippings, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 15)
      - Sales, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 16)
      - Sales: Memoranda: Anne - Harvey Chertok, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 17)
      - Schedules: Pilot and Promos, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 18)
      - Series Development: Possible Narrators and Consultants, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 19)
      - Series Proposal, undated (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 20)
      - SFX, undated (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 21)
      - Sherrod, Bob, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 22)
      - Shipping Receipts, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 23)
      - Signed Releases [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Smith, Beverly: Film Memoranda, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 24)
      - Staff, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 25)
      - Stations and Times, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 26)
      - Stills, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 27)
      - Stock Footage, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 28)
      - Stock Footage [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R62)
      - Time-Life Office Requisitions, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 29)
      - Topic Lists, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 30)
      - Travel Information, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 31)
      - Updated Proposal, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 32)
      - Vet Magazines: GI Diary Notices, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 33-34)
      - Veteran Response Sheet, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 35)
      - Veterans, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 36)
      - Veterans: Letters to be Replied to, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 37)
      - Vets and Viewer Responses, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 38)
      - Voice Over Recording Dates, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 39)
      - W4s, undated (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 40)
      - WCBS, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 41)
      - Writers' Memoranda, 1978 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 42)
      - WWII: Miscellaneous Research, 1943, 1962, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 43)
      - WWII: Promo and Graphics, 1977 (Offsite-box 3711, Folder 44)
    - Subsubseries VII.A.6.c. Letters Files, 1946, 1973-1979; 1.42 Linear feet in 3 records cartons
      The Letter Files contain materials from 1946 and 1973 to 1978. The bulk of the materials cover the period of 1977 to 1979. While it is unclear who these files belong to, Janis Klein, a producer for the series, and Beverly Smith, an associate producer for the series, were both involved in placing ads for veteran stories in military magazines and publications. It is unclear if they were also receiving and reviewing the letters as well. This subsubseries mainly contains correspondence from military veterans describing their experiences in World War II. The titles of the folders reflect the titles that the veterans or Time-Life Films Television staff assigned to the stories. There is a limited amount of other materials including clippings, notes, veteran response sheets, enlistment and separation forms from the United States military, and copies service member diaries.
      - Beagle, Betram T.: Beagles Eagles, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 6)
      - Brim, R.G.: Thoughts of a Combat Infantryman, undated (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 7)
      - Cooper, Richard: My Last Hours with Cupid, undated (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 8)
      - Dorris, Reynolds: The Sun Did Rise, undated (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 9)
      - Dye, Donald: Diary, 1972 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 10)
      - Felman, Richard: Mihailovich and I, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 11)
      - Friedman, Abe: High Tension, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 12)
      - Greek, Betty: From Johnny Who Didn't Come Marching Home, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 13)
      - Hamilton, Chuck: The Bataan Rose, undated (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 14)
      - Hamilton, Chuck: Flip and Flop, undated (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 15)
      - Hamilton, Chuck: Memories on Parade, undated (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 16)
      - Hancock, Morck: Memoirs of the 830th Engineer Aviation Battalion, 1973 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 17)
      - Herman, Ralph: Spared at the Ravine, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 18)
      - Heston, Robert: Letter, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 19)
      - Hulina, Milton: Fugitive Mariner, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 20)
      - Keilman, Myron: I Remember, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 21)
      - Kriegsman, John: Letter, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 22)
      - Larsen, Carl: Diary and Addenda, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 23)
      - Liebenow, William: The Incident: 1943 August 1-2, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 24)
      - McCool, James: Havannah Harbor, 1978 (Offsite-box 3363, Folder 25)